Olena Luhova

Phone: +4526661436

E-mail: <u>ellen.lugova@gmail.com</u> Date of birth: April 23, 1987



About Me:

I have a master's degree in international economy and management. In my previous work, as a teacher, I have had lots of experience testing different educational software and reporting bugs to my colleagues. I have also had a great deal of managerial work. My employers and colleagues would characterise me as a very responsible, communicative, and proactive person. I believe individual effort and teamwork are the key to success in achieving the common goal, so I always do my best at any task and keep in mind the company's objectives.

Skills:

Good knowledge of SDLC, STLC, Test Design Techniques, test documentation. Basic knowledge of HTML, SQL, API. Experience with bug tracking systems (Jira, Asana), Scrum.

Experience:

BeOA Today

Online course for junior QAs.

Dust Foundation

Y8

Junior QA trainee

April 2022- September 2022

Learning theory and passing oral interview.

Analysing requirements.

Decomposing web-pages and web-sites.

Creating check-lists, test cases, bug reports, test summary reports.

Participating in daily Scrum meeting and weekly retros.

Performing exploratory, regression, cross-browser, functional, and compatibility testing.

Sct. Jørgens School

Danish public school.

English Teacher

August 2022- November 2022

AllRight

Online English school for children and teenagers.

English Tutor

February 2018- June 2021

Vashi Berci

Ukrainian producer of military shoes.

Project Manager

March 2014- September 2017

Planning and monitoring website construction phase (design and functionality).

Developing, prioritising, and promoting design/content recommendations based on usability metrics.

Defining and maintaining brand identity across all ads, websites and social media channels.

MBA Strategy

Consulting and education company that aids to get admission into world top business schools. During my employment in this company I have had 3 different roles simultaneously throughout the years.

Tutor Head of TestPrep Department Head of Ukrainian Office May 2007- June 2013 January 2010- February 2014 January 2013- February 2014 Conducting group and private lessons (live, Skype, Telekom).

Creating video lessons.

Handling a wide range of administrative, technical and executive-support tasks.

FastForward LLC

Organiser of unique corporate and open management tours in the USA, Europe and Asia

Project Manager March 2013- March 2013

Support of participants in the management tour to Silicon Valley (USA).

Coordinating and compelling all clerical and day-to-day administrative support activities.

Establishing travel policies and developing procedures for expense reporting.

GoGMAT

Platform that helps people prepare for GMAT and receive high scores

Proof-Reader February 2012- January 2013

Testing test questions for compliance with the test logic.

Implementing editorial standards and guidelines for use in fund reporting, including the use of style guide.

Education:

<u>Kyiv National Economic University</u> named after Vadym Hetman
Master's degree in International Economy and Management

Professional Development:

Training for Trainers	2009
Blue Ocean Strategy	2012
Situational Leadership	2011
TOEFL 106 ETS, English	2012
Udemy Google Classroom course	2020
Udemy Teaching English as a Foreign Language TEFL course	2021
BeQA Today Junior QA engineer course	2022

Languages:

Russian and Ukrainian - native English - fluent

My LinkedIn